- Hello.  - Hello, sweetie.
- 你好!   - 你好，宝贝!
Daddy. It'S early.
爸爸  还早着呢!
I know. I juSt wanted you to know,I'm sending you something.
我知道 我想告诉你我给你寄了点东西
- Does it smell nice?  - No, but it's sparkly.
- 是不是很好闻的东西？ - 不是,是闪闪发光的东西
- Does it have a receipt? - I'm sending it to you from the store.
- 有没有收据？            -  我在商店直接寄给你的
Come by. We'll have Some breakfaSt.
你不如来我这里吧！ 我们一起吃早餐
It would be a Iong trip.
我离你可远了
I'm in Venice.
我在威尼斯
With yOur parOle Officer'S apprOval?
应该得到了假释官的批准吧？
I like the guy, Stella,but we never really connected.
那家伙我喜欢 你知道的 不过我们从没联系过
SO I think I've paid my Po hiS laSt viSit.
他最后一次造访 我已经把帐单付清了
What are yOu into? Don't break my heart. YOu Said you were through.
你要干什么？爸爸？ 你别伤了我的心  你说过你已经金盆洗手了
After thiS, I am. I Swear to yOu.
干完这次就收山 我对你发誓！
- IS Charlie there? - I'm On a cellphOne.
- 查理在吗？ - 我用手机打的电话
I'll call yOu tOmOrrOw frOm a landline.I IOve yOu. GO back tO Sleep. Bye.
我用手机打的电话  明天我会用有线打给你  我爱你 继续睡吧 再见！
Dad?
爸爸？
I IOve yOu, tOO.
我也爱你
- I Sent it. - YOu're SuppOSed tO ShOp after the jOb.
- 东西我寄了 - 要逛衔应该等到大功告成之后
I feel SO OptimiStic. HOw dO yOu feel?
我很有信心 你感觉如何？
- Fine. - Fine?
-很好 - 很好
- YOu knOw what fine StandS fOr? - Yeah, unfOrtunately.
- 你知道“好”代表什么吗？ - 很遗憾，我知道
- Freaked-Out... - InSecure...
- 兴奋过度  -“不可靠”
- NeurOtic... - And emOtiOnal.
- “神经质” - 还有“情绪化”
- See thOSe cOlumnS behind yOu? - What abOut them?
- 看见你身后那些柱子吗？- 怎么了？
That'S where they Strung up thieveS whO felt fine.
是用来绑那些自我感觉很“好”的贼
Well, after yOu.
你也跑不掉
- FOr after the haul. - HOpe I'll get tO fire it up.
- 得手之后再吸 - 希望有机会享受
NO wOrd frOm the garbage men?
收垃圾的还没消息？
NO. They dOn't ShOw, prep'S wasted and yOu're Out Of retirement fOr nOthing.
没有 如果他们不出现 准备就付诸东流 我也白劝阻你退休了
ThiS iS fun. YOu've taken Over the reinS,the wOrrieS. I'm juSt alOng fOr the ride.
这样真有趣，我喜欢 你来负责，别患得患失 我可以轻松自在 逍遥上路
Glad yOu're enjOying yOurSelf, JOhn.
好高兴你能自得其乐 约翰
POlice bOat can get tO uS in Seven, SO yOu've fOur minuteS tO wOrk yOur magic.
记住 警察乘船赶到要7分钟 也就是说只有4分钟给你施展身手
- YOu tOld me ten and Said I'd have five. - When?
- 你以前说是10分钟 这会又说5分钟 - 什么时候说的？
DO nOt meSS with me.
你别搞得我一头雾水好吗?
- I will kick yOur aSS. - Yeah? Take yOur beSt ShOt.
- 我会扁你的 - 是吗？来啊 放马过来吧！
What?
什么？
COme On, let'S gO. What iS it thiS time?
来吧 快点！你在看什么书？
Da Vinci. Architect, engineer, painter.
达・芬奇 建筑家，机械专家，画家
- FaScinating. - Check thiS Out.
- 真吸引人- 你注意听听这句话书名
"Learn the language Of pOetry, art, rOmance, Sex..."
“象达・芬奇一样思考”
Unlike yOu, my friend, I dOn't need a guidebOOk. Can we gO?
老友，我可不象你，还需要什么人生指南！能走了吗？
- Right, guvnOr. - Make yOurSelf uSeful. Untie that line.
- 遵命 老大！ - 快来干点活 把绳子松开
- TOday. - Yeah.
- 今天 - 对
Yeah, Gilligan, if yOu dOn't mind.
是的 Gilligan 如果你不介意的话
We Set?
准备好了？
Yeah. The viewing matrix tracks the Cartesian coordinates
好了 增强的电脑模型可以追踪目标的坐标及三个方向的高度
and altitude angles to give the exact position of our baby.
可以偏离 倾斜 旋转以取得目标的准确方位值
- We're in Italy. Speak EngliSh. - Steve, how we Iooking?
- 我们是在意大利 请说英语 - 史蒂夫 情况如何？
Papa tOOk the bOat at 8.15, SO the garage iS empty.
父亲在8点15乘船出去工作，所以船库会空出来
Mama left with daughter at 8.30 fOr pre-SchOOI, aS uSual,
母亲象往常一样在8点半送女儿上幼儿园
SO fOr the next 45 minuteS, we Own thiS place.
45分钟内 这个地方属于我们的, 先生们
Still nO wOrd frOm the garbage men?
收垃圾的还没有消息吗？
WhO gOt yOu the BudapeSt beekeeperS? YOu can truSt theSe guyS.
嘿, 你怎么变得这么婆婆妈妈 你应该信任这帮人
How many times must I tell you?
史蒂夫 我和你说过多少次了？
TruSt everyOne, but nOt the devil inSide them.
我什么人都信任 只是不信任内心的邪恶
We're in.
我们到了
JuSt tell me where tO paint.
告诉我在哪涂
- YOur men Still nOt in pOSitiOn? - They will be.
- 你的人还没就位？ - 他们会就位的
YOu don't knOw that. We Should abort.
你不能肯定 我们要中止计划
I think that'S Charlie'S call nOw.
我认为该由查理来作主
Our baby'S being taken away tOnight. ThiS iS Our Only ShOt.
宝贝今晚就要运离这里 现在是我们唯一的机会
- Charlie? - Keep gOing?
- 查理？- 继续？
- It'S up tO yOu, kid. - Let'S gO.
- 你拿主意 - 干吧
OK, Steve.
好了 Steve
From the west wall measure 14 feet 8 inches.
离西墙14尺8英寸
- GOt it. - 8 feet 5 inches from the north wall.
- 搞定 - 离北墙8尺5英寸
That's the northwest corner of our baby.
就是宝贝的位置
- GOt it. - Well, it'S right abOve yOu.
- 搞定 - 好了，就在你正上方
Now, paint. 2 feet 9 inches wide 2 feet 5 inches deep.
开始涂吧 2尺9英寸宽 2尺5英寸长
OK, Left Ear, yOu're up. 14 feet 4 incheS frOm that weSt wall.
好了 左耳 该你了 离西墙14尺4英寸
The garbage men are in pOSitiOn, JOhn.
收垃圾的已就位 John
They've gOt the Safe in the bOat!
保险箱在船上
SOmeOne juSt called it in. The pOlice bOat'S heading yOur way.
有人报警了  警察正向你方赶来
Seven minuteS and cOunting. Let'S gO.
7分钟计时  动手吧
We've gOt fOur minuteS. Let'S gO.
4分钟时间装货 动手吧
Hey, yOu guyS. COme here.
嘿 小伙子们 过来这里
I want tO prOpOSe a tOaSt.
我提议碰一碰
TO uS!
为我们
And I want tO prOpOSe a tOaSt tO Charlie.
然后再为Charlie喝一口
We juSt StOle 35 milliOn dOllarS wOrth Of gOld withOut even hOlding a gun
不发一枪就到手价值3500万的金子
because he planned this down to a T
全归功于他计划周详
NObOdy elSe cOuld've dOne that. Charlie!
这点没人做得到 Charlie!
SO, cOme On. ShOpping liStS. WhO'S dOing what? Spare nO dirty detailS.
来吧，先生吧 计划一下购物清单和活动 可以花个痛快了
COme On, guyS. Take a leSSOn frOm an Old man. DOn't Spend it. InveSt.
算了 小伙子 听老汉一言 钱不要乱花 去投资
- In what? - In gOld.
- 投资什么？ - 投资到金子上
- Let'S get Out Of here firSt. - What are yOu getting, ROb?
- 还是先考虑如何离开这里吧 - 你打算买什么？
I dOn't knOw. There'S a IOt Of thingS yOu can buy.
我不知道，好多东西想买
I'm thinking Of naked girlS and leather SeatS. I'll get the AStOn Martin VanquiSh.
现在 我正幻想拥抱着真皮椅上的裸女 来部阿斯顿・马汀
There'S little a girl wOn't dO in One Of thOSe.
没多少女孩不愿意坐在这种车上
I'm getting a NAD T770 digital decOder, 70-watt ampS and Burr-BrOwn DACS.
我要买一套NADT770功放 70瓦功率 使用伯尔布朗芯片
It'S a big StereO with SpeakerS SO IOud they blOw wOmen'S clOtheS Off.
这可是功率巨大的系统 喇叭声大到可以帮女人宽衣解带
$35 million and you can't get more creative than that?
3千5百万啊 不能花得有点创意吗？
I'm gOing tO AndaluSia, SOuth Of Spain,
我要去AndaluSia 西班牙南部
get me a big hOuSe, a library Of firSt editiOnS, a rOOm fOr my ShOeS.
买一幢豪宅 搞个收藏首版书的图书馆 辟个房间专门放我的鞋
- What abOut yOu, Steve? - I haven't decided yet.
- 你呢 史蒂夫? - 不知道，还没有想好
YOu haven't decided yet? IS it the mOuntain air?
还没想好了？ 是不是因为高山缺氧？
I liked what yOu Said. I'll take One each Of yOurS.
我要博取众长 大家的建议都会采纳一些.
Well, twO Of everything fOr Steve.
多采纳一些 为Steve
I IOved the tOaSt. But yOu cOuld've pulled thiS Off with yOur eyeS clOSed.
还在回味吗  你闭着眼也能把保险箱搞定
YOu were juSt incredible.
你表现的令人不可思议
YOu Saw the whOle picture and cOvered all the angleS.
你计划周密 纵观全局
Charlie, there are twO kindS Of thieveS in thiS wOrld.
Charlie 在这个世界上有两种贼
The OneS whO Steal tO enrich their liveS,
一种是为钱而偷
and the OneS whO Steal tO define their liveS.
一种是为偷而偷
DOn't be the latter. YOu miSS Out On what'S really impOrtant in thiS life.
别成为后者 这样会使你忽略人生要义
What are yOu talking abOut? YOu've been a gOOd father.
你是什么意思？ 你是个好父亲
Sitting in priSOnS dOeSn't make yOu a gOOd father.
身陷囹囵可成不了慈父
I've Spent half my kid'S life in priSOn. DOn't get tO my age with Only thiS.
女儿出生后 我有一半时间在牢里渡过 到我这把年纪你可别象我这样
Find SOmebOdy yOu want tO Spend the reSt Of yOur life with. And hOld On tO her.
去寻找可与你共渡余生的人 并与她一生相守
Hey, let'S gO. I'm freezing my aSS Off.
嘿 走吧 我都快冻僵了
- Steve'S getting cOld. YOu, tOO?  - I'm all right.
- Steve快冻僵了 你也是吗？ - 我没事
- I IOve yOu, kid. YOu did really great. - ThankS, JOhn.
- 我爱你，孩子 你很出色 - 多谢 JOhn
Let'S gO.
走吧
ROb waS driving that bOat like Don Johnson!
可惜你们没看到ROb开船的英姿就象Don Johnson一样
- Yeah, frOm Brixton. - What dO yOu knOw abOut BrixtOn?
- 是，从Brixton来 - 你知道Brixton？
LOOk at thiS idiOt in the middle Of the rOad.
路中间那傻车怎么开的
What'S thiS?
怎么回事？
WhO the hell are theSe guyS?
这是帮什么人？
- Take yOur handS Off the wheel. - Steve
- 把手从方向盘拿开 - Steve
JuSt dO it.
不要搞什么花样
NO, John.
John别
- What the hell are yOu dOing? - Made a few planS Of my Own.
- 你在搞什么鬼？ - 实施我个人的一些计划
There'S nOwhere yOu can gO we wOn't find yOu.
你上天入地我们都会把你挖出来
I think that'S prObably right.
你说得对极了
GO! GO!
快开 快开
We've gOt tO gO, Charlie.
我们得走了  Charlie
- DO yOu alwayS wOrk in the dark? - MakeS me feel I'm alOne.
- 你怎么老是摸黑工作？ -让我有种孤独感
NOt bad, Stella.
不错 Stella
- Purley cOuldn't crack that Safe. - Neither cOuld Spears.
- Purley没法打开这个保险箱 - Spears也不行
- YOu knOw whO tO call firSt. - YOu're expenSive.
- 现在你知道该找谁了吧 - 你收费太高了
Those guys cut us a break on subpoena jobs, goodwill...
上头削减我们的经费用于传讯及感化服务......
I dO it fOr the mOney. I'll Send yOu a bill.
我工作是为了钱 我会把帐单寄给你
- DOn't yOu want tO See inSide? - I never IOOk inSide.
- 不想看看里面有什么？ - 我从来不看里面
Have a gOOd day. Hey, George.
祝你好运 你好 George
- HOw IOng tO crack it? - FOur minuteS, 43 SecOndS.
- 开锁用了多长时间？ - 4分43秒
- YOu're the man. - What'S in the line-up?
- 噢！你真厉害 - 都有此什么事要我处理
Todd Millikan called. He haS a prOtOtype IOck he wantS yOu tO teSt.
Todd 打来电话 他手头有一把号码锁的原型 他想要你去校验
He added twO falSe cOntact pOintS On the tumbler.
他说他在锁的制栓上附加了 两个假的接触点
I'll pretend tO be Stumped fOr a SecOnd Or twO.
我得假装被难住了 让他高兴一下
And there'S a Charlie Croker in yOur Office. SayS yOu knOw each Other.
有位Charlie Croker先生在你办公室
- Charlie Croker. - Hi, Stella.
- Charlie Croker - 你好 Stella
Didn't I tell yOu I never want tO See yOu again?
难道我没告诉你 我不想再见到你
It waS when yOu tOld me my father died after yOu pulled him in fOr One laSt jOb.
你告诉我是你让父亲最后一次出手 然后他在你眼皮底下死去
We fOund him, Stella. He'S in LOS AngeleS.
我们找到Stella了 在LOS AngeleS
The gOld brickS he StOle frOm uS had a BalineSe dancer Stamped On them.
他从我们这偷走的金砖上刻着巴厘岛舞娘女
My cOntact, Skinny Pete, SayS an LA dealer'S been buying thOSe brickS.
我从一个叫Skinny Pete的朋友那收到风 洛杉矶有个大买家正在吃进这批金砖
- HOw dO yOu knOw it'S him? - Skinny Pete Sent me thiS.
- 你怎么知道是他？ - Skinny Pete给我的
Steve changed hiS laSt name tO Frizelli.
Steve把姓改为Frizelli
- Why tell me thiS? - I checked high-end Safe cOmpanieS.
- 你告诉我这些做什么？ - 我查了安全保卫公司的数据库
Steve had a WOrthingtOn 1000 delivered tO hiS hOme Office.
有一套渥新顿1000系统寄到Steve的公司
YOu inStall a WOrthingtOn 1000 Only if yOu've gOt SOmething big tO guard.
你没有安装Worthington 1000 除非你有重要的东西需要保管
NO One On my crew can handle it.I need SOmebOdy I can truSt.
问题是我们无法对付Steve这套安全系统 而我需要一些足以信赖的人
I'm a Safe technician. I'm nOt a thief.
我是保险箱及保险库的技术专家 我可不是贼
It'S nOt abOut the gOld, Stella. John waS like a father tO me, tOO.
不只是为了金子 Stella John 我也视之如父
I'm SOrry. I can't mOve On until I've Set thingS right.
对不起 此仇不报我无法释怀
I've mOved On.
我已经释怀了
COme On, then, Charlie. COme On.
来吧  Charlie 来吧
I want tO See hiS face when hiS gOld iS gOne.
我想看看那人两手空空的样子
He took my father, I'm taking this.
他害死了我父亲 我要报仇
- She'S in. - That'S a gOOd thing?
- 她要出手了 - 算是好事吗？
She can crack the WOrthingtOn 1000 withOut flinching.
她可以干净利索地破解渥新顿1000
I'm nOt Sure hiring a civilian'S a gOOd idea.
一位守法公民加入我们 不一定是好事
- She'S gOt the SkillS and the mOtivatiOn. - Exactly.
- 她有技术也有动机 - 没错
She'S emOtiOnal. YOu knOw what happenS then.
她也很情绪化 你知道掺入个人情绪是什么结果
DOn't kid yOurSelf. We're all emOtiOnal On thiS One. Let'S gO.
别自欺欺人了 我们都带着情绪 来吧
- Are yOu ready? - COurSe I am.
- 准备好没有？ - 没准备好
YOu're nOt ready.
你没准备好
- That waS quick. - Where are they?
- 好快 - 他们呢？
We're a little early. I didn't expect uS tO get here that faSt.
我们来早了点 我没想到这么快到
There. That'S Lyle. He'S my cOmputer geniuS.
那里 Lyle来了 他是个电脑天才
He'S whO really invented NapSter. At leaSt, that'S hOw he tellS it.
他是Napster(著名音乐共享软件)真正作者 至少Lyle是这么说的
Said Shawn Fanning waS hiS cOllege rOOm-mate and StOle hiS idea.
他说Fanning(Napster作者)是他的室友 把他的创意给偷了
I think it'S hiS firSt time riding that bike, thOugh.
他第一次骑那部摩托
- YOu OK? - Yeah.
- 没事吧？ - 没事
That'S Left Ear. DemOlitiOn and explOSiveS.
那是左耳 爆破专家
When he waS ten he put tOO many M80S in the tOilet bOwl.
10岁的时候在马桶里放了太多M-80 结果爆炸了
- COOI! HOw did yOu dO that? - What?
- 真酷 怎么做到的？ - 什么？
- HOw did yOu dO that? - What?
- 你怎么做到的？ - 什么？
What?
什么？
LOSt hearing in hiS right ear. BIOwn Stuff up ever Since.
他右耳因此丧失听力 从那以后他就开始东炸西爆
HandSOme ROb. Premier wheelman.
大帅哥ROb超级车手
Once drOve frOm LA juSt SO he cOuld Set the freeway chaSe recOrd.
有一次曾经跑遍洛杉矶所有的路 只是为了创造最长追车记录
He got 110 love letters from women who saw him on the news.
他在监狱里收到110封求爱信 全是电视上对他一见钟情的女人写的
And yOu? I never heard hOw yOu gOt yOur Start.
你呢？ 那你的经历呢？
Me? Well, I've been a thief Since I had baby teeth.
我？我乳臭未干就是个小贼
- OK, yOu bOth knOw what tO dO. - COugh it up nOw.
- 好了 你们俩都知道怎么做了 - 交出来
Watch it, SpaS! What'S yOur prOblem, man?
看着 笨蛋！嘿，你想干吗，小子？
- Hey, Charlie. - GOOd tO See yOu.
- 嘿 Charlie - 见到你很高兴
GOOd tO See yOu.
见到你很高兴
- HellO, Charlie. - YOu gOOd?
- 你好 Charlie - 还好吗
GuyS, Stella Bridger.
兄弟们 Stella Bridger
- Nice tO meet yOu. - PhOneS.
- 见到你很高兴 - 电话呢？
They're all clean, with internal chipS. Change daily, we will get heat Online.
电话全是新的这里是内部的芯片 请每天更换两次
IDS?
身份证呢？
JameS Hymen? One time give me a cOOI name.
JameS Hymen？别这样 哥们给我个好名字
- 140 pOundS? Try 165. - Try lifting SOme weightS.
- 140磅？还不如写165 - 你增加点体重吧
- Try lifting up theSe. - We leave tOmOrrOw, all right?
- 好了 伙计们 -我们明天出发 是吗？
- HandSOme, help him with the bike. - Help Knievel Set up hiS next jump.
- 帅哥 帮他整整那部摩托 - 好的 为他再摔一次作准备
Out Of all the placeS fOr a thief tO hide, thiS jOker picked HOllywOOd.
世上这么多藏身之地中 这个家伙选中了好莱坞
He'S a punk, but he ain't Stupid.
他是个混蛋 不过还有点脑子
We need a way tO make a blueprint Of the inSide Of Steve'S hOuSe.
我们得想办法进入Steve的家中拍个内部结构图的摄像
- I want phOne Surveillance. - I want tO try SOmething.
- 我要监听他的电话 - 好 我来想想办法
I'll fOOI the phOne cOmpany intO thinking there'S a legal tap On the line
我侵入电话公司的远程监控系统做些手脚使系统认为对某线路的监听合法
and re-rOute the cOpieS Of the callS tO uS.Been dOing it tO my ex fOr yearS.
将话音转接到我们自己的监听电话上 我监听过我前妻好几年
HOw IOng... will it take? NOt, hOw IOng have yOu been dOing it tO yOur ex?
多长时间？是问你办成需要多长时间 不是问你监听了老婆电话多长时间？
- I'll have it running by mOrning. - SOrry I'm late.
- 熬个通宵 应该早上就可以了 - 对不起 我迟到了
We gOtta get Steve Out Of the hOuSe.  HOw much time dO yOu need?
我们要设法让Steve走出家门 斯特拉，破解需要多长时间？
- Five minuteS flat. - DOn't be cOcky.
- 5分钟足已 - 别太自负了，小妞
It'S nOt the Same aS Opening a Safe fOr the pOlice.
这可不是替警察打开个保险箱
PerSpiratiOn On yOur fingertipS, heart'S pOunding. WhOle different ball game.
你的手会紧张得冒汗心会砰砰乱跳 完全是两码事
I appreciate yOur cOncern. I'll be fine.
多谢你的关心，我行的
ThiS iS the eaSy part. The getaway can get uS caught.
上面所说是最容易的行动 我们最可能失手的地方就是在逃跑过程中
- What'S the Schedule? - Drive tO UniOn StatiOn.
- 说说计划 - 我们开车到联合车站
Car gOeS OntO the train. We need tO knOw exactly hOw IOng tO UniOn StatiOn.
连车一起乘上火车  我们要知道从Steve家到联合车站的准确时间
- Oh, great. Carson Security SyStem. - HOw gOOd iS it?
- 好极了 Carson安全系统 - 性能如何？
Carson'S hOld an annual cOnteSt. $50,000 if you can bypass the system.
Carson公司每年举办一次竞赛 通过此系统者可获5万美金
It'S a whO'S whO Of ex-cOnS. Five yearS running, nO One'S been paid.
挑战者络绎不绝  比赛连办5年 没人拿到过那笔钱
Here'S the StatuS.
我描述这里的情况
An anti-Scaling fence, hardened electrO-plated Steel.
不锈钢栅栏 坚硬电镀钢条所制
I'll have tO paint that up with SOme nitrOmOn.
我会把盐酸氮芥涂到栅栏上的
- Security? - A little rent-a-cOp with a 9 mm.
- 保安？- 一把9MM口径手枪
That security booth looks prime for a chemical grenade.
保安亭很合麻醉手榴弹的胃口
Nitromon, chemical grenades? That stuff's hard to come by.
保安亭 麻醉手榴弹？ 盐酸氮芥麻醉手榴弹这些东西不容易搞到
Yeah, Lyle, it'S a bear market... Shit!
对 Lyle  有价无市 妈的
ThiS dude gOt dOgS. I dOn't dO dOgS. I had a real bad
这公子哥居然养了狗  狗我可应付不来 我曾有过惨痛经历
- What happened? - I had a bad experience. I'm deaf?
- 怎么了？ - 我有过惨痛经历 我聋了？
"Turn in yOur badge and yOur weapOn..." CruSh.
“交出你的徽章和武器”
"I dOn't want yOu anywhere near thiS inveStigatiOn.
“这桩案子里我不想见到你出现
"...yOur badge and yOur weapOn.
交出你的徽章和武器
"I dOn't want yOu anywhere near thiS inveStigatiOn."
这桩案子里我不想见到你出现
Oi! Lt'S a green!
嘿！绿灯了
Green!
绿灯
Unbelievable.
真不敢相信
There he iS.
他现身了
Let'S get tO wOrk.
干活吧
It'S either bad traffic, peak traffic Or Slit-yOur-wriSt traffic.
到处都是堵车塞车 交通瘫痪
Five peOple died frOm SmOking between traffic lightS.
今天有5个人在交通堵塞期间吸烟致死
YOu cOuld alwayS uSe the metrO.
我们应该乘地铁
That wOuld be ideal fOr carrying a tOnne Of gOld.
带着一大堆黄金坐地铁 真是个高招
What'S yOur gueSStimate?
你预测的时间是多少？
FrOm 20 jOurneyS, I gOt an average Of 32 minuteS and a tOp time Of 50.
按我最后20次的时间计算  平均32分钟，最长50分钟
But with green lightS, we cOuld dO it in 14 minuteS.
如果一路绿灯 14分钟可以到达
What, yOu cOuldn't get thrOugh traffic?
不堵车有可能吗？
YOu cOuld dO anything with green lightS all the way.
如果一路绿灯我们就不用担心了
I'll See what I can dO.
我尽力而为吧
YOu're right On time.
你很准时
TheSe peOple putting their SavingS in bankS, S and LS, mutual fundS...
这些可怜的傻瓜把全付身家都放在银行和共有基金里
DO they think when the cOllapSe cOmeS they can depend On the gOvernment?
不知道他们怎么想的银行倒闭的时候 难道政府指望得上吗？
- I dOn't think SO. - Are yOu taping me?
- 我可不觉得 - 你把我录下来了？
Of cOurSe nOt. I never tape yOu. See fOr yOurSelf.
我从来没录过你 过来看你自己看
GOvernmentS are nOthing mOre than puppetS On StringS.
政府只是个傀儡而已
In a wOrld where NAFTA can Overrule the Supreme COurt,
北美贸易协会可以支配最高法院
like my cOuSin MaShkOv alwayS SayS, "ThiS iS Our Only refuge, baby."
就象我表弟口头禅 “这才是我们的庇护神，宝贝”
GOld.
金子
Every time I IOOk at theSe engravingS... She'S SO beautiful.
每次我看着这些雕刻 总觉得是如此美丽
- Where did yOu Say yOu gOt theSe? - I didn't.
- 你说你从哪搞来的？ - 我没说过
A little "walking arOund" mOney.
一点黑金
- I'm nOt walking aS far aS I thOught.  - I can Only buy twO tOday.
- 数目和我想象的不一样 - 很抱歉 今天我只能买两条
- That waSn't the agreement. - I'm juSt middleman.
- 协议可不是这样的 - 我只是个中间人
- I'll buy the Other twO On WedneSday. - DOn't waSte my time, Yevhen.
- 星期三我会买下另外两条 - 别浪费我的时间
SO, what dOeS a man with 35 milliOn dOllarS wOrth Of gOld dO at night?
身家3千5百万的男人晚上会干什么？
He watcheS hiS big-aSS TV.
不过看个狗屁电视
That'S Our in.
该干活了
JeSuS!
- HOw did yOu get in here? - I knOcked but yOu didn't anSwer.
- 你怎么进来的？ - 我敲了门 你没回答
- SO yOu juSt let yOurSelf in? - I waS checking yOu were OK. I'm SOrry.
- 所以你就闯进来了？- 我只是担心你的安全 我道歉
DOn't IOOk.
别看
OK.
好了
YOu've gOt a IOt Of Stuff. YOur dad waS Old SchOOI.
令尊是个守旧派
- Did the whOle thing by tOuch. - It wOrked fOr him. ThiS wOrkS fOr me.
- 全凭触觉干活 - 蛇有蛇路 鼠有鼠道
TechnOIOgy guaranteeS Speed and accuracy.
技术可以保证速度和精确
There'S nO guaranteeS in thiS buSineSS, Stella. Why the headphOneS?
我们干的事可没什么保证 Stella 耳机用来作什么？
JuSt training mySelf. Ambient nOiSeS, yOu knOw. JuSt in caSe.
只是用于自我训练 环境噪声 为了以防万一
- What dO yOu want? - We're knOcking Out Steve'S cable.
- 你有什么事吗 - 我们会破坏Steve家中的电缆
- Then we Send in a repair man. - TO get yOur videO blueprint?
- 然后派个修理工进去 - 拍下内部结构的摄像
Yeah. The prOblem iS Steve thinkS we're all dead.
问题是Steve以为我们都死了
Except me.
除了我
I'll dO it, Charlie. I'm in all the way. Whatever it takeS.
我来干吧 Charlie 我会想方设法办到的
- All right. I'll Set it up. - OK.
- 好吧 我会安排好的 - 好的
YOu want tO get a drink with me befOre I gO back tO my rOOm?
在睡觉之前想不想出去喝杯饮料？
I ShOuld finiSh thiS Stuff up. Get it all dOne tOnight.
我得把事干完 今天要把这些都弄好
- Yeah. SOrry I Scared yOu. - It'S OK.
- 好的 吓着你 真对不起 - 没关系
GOOdnight.
晚安
Bye.
再见
Then he'S the media darling, On all the magazine cOverS.
他是媒体的宠儿 上了所有杂志的封面
I ShOuld've been On Wired magazine'S cOver.
我也应该上连线杂志的封面
He Said he named it NapSter becauSe Of hiS nickname, hiS nappy hair,
他说是他命名为Napster 这是他的绰号 他 -的卷发
but it'S 'cauSe I waS napping when he StOle it frOm me.
明明是因为他偷东西时我在打盹
- He didn't even graduate. - I think it'S time tO mOve On, dOn't yOu?
- 他连业都没毕 - 你该把这事忘记了
They Shut him dOwn. I wiSh they'd dO the Same tO yOu.
他的公司也关闭了 我希望你的嘴也一起关闭
Here. Here we gO. Cable chick.
有活干了  Cable chick
Becky. Nice name. I wOnder what She callS the Other One.
Becky 好名字 不知道她怎么称呼其他人
It'S Such a myStery why yOu dOn't have a girlfriend.
你没有女朋友真的好奇怪
All we need iS a Service truck like that, a wOrk-Shirt like herS...
我们需要一部这样的设备车  一件这样的工作服
- Think Stella can pull it Off? - I have my dOubtS.
- 你觉得Stella能成功吗？ - 我也拿不准
There'S nO talking tO Charlie, thOugh.
我也拿不准
YOu think he'S mixing buSineSS with pleaSure?
你认为寓工作于娱乐之中？
He ShOuld knOw better. Only I'm allOwed tO dO that.
这事他自己才清楚 我只管干好我的活
Right. Where are yOu gOing?
好的 你要去哪里？
The wOrk-Shirt and the Service truck.
Are yOu kidding me?
你不是耍我吧？
HOw dOeS he dO that? HOw dO yOu dO that? What are yOu Saying?
他打算怎么办？ 看你怎么办 你在说什么？
"Hey, hOw are yOu?" "I'm gOOd."
“嗨，你好吗？”“噢, 我很好”
"Nice tO meet yOu, I'm HandSOme ROb, and yOu are?"
“幸会，我是ROb帅哥 你叫…？”
"My name'S Becky. It'S On my Shirt."
“噢, 我叫 Becky 我的制服上写着”
"I need yOur Shirt and yOur truck."
“听着, 我需要你的制服和车子”
"Perfect. WOuld yOu like my virginity aS well?"
好啊 我双手奉上 要不要连我的
"If it'S On the menu." "YOu're SO witty. Take advantage Of me."
“菜单上有吗？” “你好幽默啊 你怎么不利用我呢？”
"YOu're nOt tOO bright, are yOu?" "NO." "Perfect."
“你好幽默啊 ” “你怎么不利用我呢？” “是的”“太好了”
- YeS, Mr Frizelli. - The cable's out.
- 有什么可以效劳 Frizelli先生？ - 线路不通了
The TV, the mOdem, everything. Get SOmebOdy up here quick.
电视，调制解调器 所有设备都出问题了 快找人过来 动作快点
Netcom Cable.
这里是网通公司
I'm at 3320 East Skyway and the cable's gone.
我是东大道3320 我这里线路不通
- I have a Thursday between 9 and 3. - That's good. Thank you.
- 周四九点到三点之间  - 好的 谢谢
Guard juSt called the cable cOmpany.
警卫刚打电话给线路公司
- What time'S the appOintment? - ThurSday between 9 and 3.
- 约在几点？ - 周四九点至三点
I'm calling frOm NetcOm Cable.
YOu Set up an appOintment fOr ThurSday?
原来安排在周四上门？
We have a technician whO'S free earlier than expected.
我们有位技术员刚完成任务 完成时间比预期要早
- Will SOmebOdy be there fOr an hOur? - Sure.
- 你们那有人在吗？ - 有人，太好了
Our technician will See yOu then. Have a nice day.
我们的技术员会过去的 祝你今天愉快
Here'S all the paperwOrk yOu need. JuSt get him tO Sign and date it.
这是你需要的文件 让他在下面签上名字和日期即可
Let'S check Out the camera.
检查一下摄像机
Stella, yOu'll be gOing patriOtic tOday.
Stella 今天你是英雄
Walk SIOwly Or the image'll Streak.
走路要慢一点 否则图象就会抖动
- I'm SOrry. - It'S OK.
- 对不起 - 没关系
COuldn't pin the cOrSage On my prOm date, either.
不好意思，毕业舞会的时候 我也别不上
- YOu had a prOm date? - It waS hiS cOuSin.
- 你参加过毕业舞会？ - 那是他表兄
There'S cable in the kitchen, living rOOm, bedrOOm and the Office.
在厨房，客厅和卧室都有电缆 调制解调器在办公室的电脑上
YOu need tO IOcate the Safe in the Office.
你必须找到办公室的保险箱
I think yOu're very brave gOing in there.
我相信你能勇敢无畏地面对一切
- I SecOnd that. - It'S gOing tO be fine.
- 我也是 - 一切都会好的
What?
怎么了？
Fine StandS fOr freaked Out, inSecure...
兴奋过度，不可靠
...neurOtic and emOtiOnal.
神经质，情绪化
- YOu'll be great. - Yeah.
- 你很了不起 -
GOOd mOrning. Can I See SOme ID?
早晨好 能看看你的证件吗？
- ThankS fOr cOming SO SOOn. - That'S part Of the jOb.
- 多谢你这么快赶来 - 这是我的职责
Aston Martin Vanquish. SO that baStard tOOk my car.
Aston Martin 这王八蛋把我的车抢走了
NaSty-aSS dOgS.
臭狗
Cease!
好了！
Relax, JeSuS ChriSt!
放松 天啊
Come on, they won't bother you now.
下来吧 不会再骚扰你了
COme On. HOuSe!
下来吧 进屋去
GO On, get Out Of here.
快点走 没关系，
I'm uSed tO running intO animalS On my jOb.
工作中我经常会遇上各种动物
- Want tO ShOw me that prOblem? - Of cOurSe. ThiS way.
- 带我看看哪里出了问题 - 好  没问题  这边来
- YOu've a really nice hOuSe. - 1922. All the Original tileS.
- 你的屋子真不错 - 1922年 瓷砖都没换过
Every StOne in that cOurtyard frOm SOme mOnaStery in Seville.
院子里的每块石头都是来自于塞维尔的修道院
- What a tactic. - MOnaStery fOr punk-aSS creepS!
- 修道院？ - 修道院被这个杂种侮辱了
You're not impressed?
你好象无动于衷
Lt'S juSt that lugging rOckS frOm One place tO anOther iSn't that intereSting.
把一大堆石头从一个地方搬到另一地方 我不觉得特别有趣
- It dOeSn't quite dO it fOr me. - What dOeS dO it fOr yOu?
- 对我来说没多大意思 - 那你觉得什么有意思？
TVS.
电视
I have a mOnSter TV.
我有部大电视
- It'S nOt wOrking right nOw... - I ShOuld check the cable mOdem.
- 可惜现在用不了了 - 我要帮你检查一下调制解调器
Yeah? OK, right. Over here.
好的 这边来
I paid thirty grand fOr SOme punk kid tO inStall it. One day it juSt gOeS Out.
这套系统我花了3万美元  可它却突然罢工了
I'm gOing tO have him Strung up.
我恨不得吊死装系统的那家伙
- Here we gO. - There'S Our baby.
- 这边来 - 那就是我们的宝贝
- Oh, man. - We gOt him.
- 天啦 - 找到了
- GOt any wiring cOming thrOugh here? - There'S nO wiring in here.
- 电缆从这里穿过吗？ -这里没电缆
It'S juSt right here?
那是这儿
LOOk at that. That'S my NAD T770. That'S my StereO.
看啊，这是我的NADT770 这是我的音响
I bet peOple are SurpriSed when they expect the cable man
大伙一定都非常吃惊 除了那些通讯技术员
and find yOu Standing there.
你这么漂亮
He'S hitting On her.
他在挑逗她
There'S nO prOblem here. I ShOuld juSt check the TVS.
这里没问题 我得去查查电视
YOu knOw what? I'm blOwing thiS Shit right Off the mOuntain right nOw.
我要过去宰了这个王八羔子
- ABM prOceSSOr. - Only the beSt.
- 你用的是ABM处理器 - 我只用最好的
Check the box.
看下盒子
I'm just going to reset your system.
我要复位系统
SOmetimeS theSe thingS juSt get jammed up, yOu knOw?
有时可能是信号堵塞了
- That ShOuld dO it. - It'S fixed?
- 应该没问题了 - 修好了吗？
- Turn her On. Let'S See. - Now.
- 把电视打开试试  - 动手
Perfect.
太好了
Becky, huh? Have we met befOre?
Becky 对吧？ 我们以前见过面吗？
NO, I dOn't think SO. If yOu can juSt Sign there.
不 我想没见过 你在这里签个字
If I aSked yOu tO dinner, wOuld I be the firSt cuStOmer tO dO that?
如果我请你吃晚饭的话 会不会成为第一个提出这种要求的客户？
Did yOu aSk yOur laSt cable guy Out?
上次来的技术员 你也请他吃饭？
NO, but he waS 300 pOundS with a handlebar mOuStache.
没有，上次那位体重300磅 留着八字胡
- NOt my type. - It'S nOt a gOOd idea.
- 不是我喜欢的类型 - 这不是个好主意
- IS that SOme cable cOmpany rule? - NO, it'S my rule.
- 公司有规定吗？ - 没有 其实这是我的原则
I dOn't gO Out with Strange men. We juSt met five minuteS agO.
我不和陌生人约会我才认识你5分钟
I gueSS I have tO SabOtage my cable until we get tO knOw each Other.
那我得时常故意把线路搞坏 以便我们有足够的时间熟悉
- Have a nice day. - I'll be a perfect gentleman.
- 祝你好运 - 我保证我会很有绅士风度
I wOn't even aSk fOr yOur number. I'll meet yOu. Anywhere yOu want tO gO.
我甚至连你的电话号码都没要 我只是想认识你 你愿意去哪都成
COme On, break yOur rule. Once.
违背你的原则一次吧
JuSt dinner.
吃个晚饭而已
IS that a yeS?
算是答应吗？
YOu OK?
你没事吧？
Yeah.
没事
He tOuched my hand.
他碰了我的手
He came On tO me.
他骚扰我
Hey, at leaSt I created a windOw Of OppOrtunity, right?
不过至少我制造了一个机会
When he gOeS Out Friday night, we gO in.
他周五晚上 一出去我们就动手
By the time he realiSeS yOu've StOOd him up, we'll be gOne with that gOld.
等他意识到你于他不利 我们早已带着金子远去
Shuffle them cardS thiS time, Left.
这次你得好好把牌洗洗
Lyle, what'S the diStance between the frOnt dOOr and the vault?
Lyle 前门和保险库的距离是多少？
- Quit dealing while my back'S turned. - YOu've gOt IOSer'S paranOia.
- 别趁我转身就耍花招 - 你这是输红了眼
He Only anSwerS tO the NapSter nOw, Charlie.
叫他Napster他才理 Charlie
- I'm nOt calling yOu the NapSter. - YOu call him Left Ear.
- 我不会叫你Napster - 你叫他左耳
- And him HandSOme ROb. - BecauSe he iS HandSOme ROb.
- 他帅哥ROb - 因为他就是帅哥
- Well, yOu can call me the NapSter. - They were at cOllege tOgether.
- 那你得叫我Napster  - 他们也算在同一所大学读书
- Why are yOu encOuraging thiS? - It iS verifiable.
- 你为什么要鼓励他？ - 可这是事实
He waS my rOOm-mate. He StOle my ideaS. I am the NapSter.
他是我的室友 偷走了我的创意 我才是Napster
All right, what iS the diStance between the frOnt dOOr and the vault, NapSter?
好了 好了 前门和保险库之间的距离是多少 Napster？
- Farther than yOu want tO carry it. - SO, hOw dO we get the gOld tO the car?
- 想徒手搬运是不可能的 - 我们怎么才能把金子从保险库搬到车上？
HOw wide iS the hallway... NapSter?
走廊是多宽 Napster？
6 feet.
6英尺
OK, yOu've gOt yOur gOld.
好的, 金子装好了
We need mOre carS tO handle the weight.
这些重量车子承受不了
I'll need help with the cuStOm wOrk. I knOw a man fOr the jOb.
我需要找人帮忙  我认识一个人精于此道
I mOdified the camera with LIDAR SO we can create hi-reS digital mapS...
我修改了一下摄像机  就样我们就能建立高清晰度的电子地图
- WhO'S that? - ROb'S mechanic friend.
- 那是谁？ - ROb的技工朋友
- Charlie, thiS iS Wrench. - What'S up?
- Charlie 这是Wrench - 你好啊
ROb SayS yOu're talented. I need SOme bOdywOrk dOne.
ROb说你精于此道 我们需要找人帮忙
We need tO pack  2,700 pOundS in theSe MiniS,
用这些小车运走 2700磅的货物
with enOugh SuSpenSiOn and hOrSepOwer tO Outrun anything chaSing.
小车还得有足够的马力摆脱追踪
- 2,700 pOundS Of what? - Whatever.
- 2700磅，是什么货物？ - 你别管了
- What dO I get frOm thiS myStery? - 10,000.
- 我可从中获得多少报酬？ -10000美元
All right.
好的
We didn't get a chance tO meet yet. Wrench.
还没机会认识一下 扳手
- Ham and cheeSe. - That'S cOld. Damn, that'S cOld.
- 我叫火腿乳酪 -  好酷 太酷了
YOu want all greenS? 'CauSe yOu gOt 'em.
想要一路绿灯吗？想要就办得到
WelcOme tO LA'S AutOmated Traffic Surveillance and COntrOI Center.
欢迎来到洛杉矶交通监控及管理中心
They uSe videO feedS frOm interSectiOnS and algOrithmS
他们采用特别设计的算法 根据十字路口采集的视频信号
tO predict traffic cOnditiOnS and cOntrOI traffic lightS.
来预测交通状况 进而控制路口的红绿灯信号
I created my Own kick-aSS algOrithm tO Sneak in
我把我设计的算法篡改进去
and nOw we Own the place.
我们就能控制交通了
- Want tO dO a dry run? - ThOught yOu'd never aSk.
- 你不想演示一下吗？ - 我还以为你不会提这种要求
See red light? Green light.
看见吗？红灯  绿灯
- DanielSOn, what'S up with grid 34? - Let'S check it Out.
- DanielSOn 34号区怎么回事？ - 我们查一查
OOpS! Did I? But it'S aweSOme. IS that nOt aweSOme?
噢 我 真的很了不起，对吧？
Can yOu change it back?
能马上改回来吗？
LightS are wOrking fine. It'S juSt an accident.
红绿灯恢复正常 一起小事故
That'S gOOd.
很好
- What are thOSe? - UnneceSSary partS.
- 这些是什么？ - 不需要的发动机零件
I IOSt yOur SmOg cOntrOIS and 200 pOundS Of fat.
我拆了除烟装置车身减重200磅
YOu gOt a Sweet ride nOw, Charlie.
Charlie 你现在有了部好车
KnOw what I'm thinking abOut right nOw? The IOOk On Steve'S face.
知道我在想什么吗？ 看看Steve的脸
- YOu're early. - I'm in a hurry.
- 你来早了 - 我很急
YOu knOw that the FIOrida vOte-rigging waS a CIA and mOb OperatiOn?
知道佛罗里达的选票 是由CIA及黑帮操纵的啊？
Which iS nOt SO different frOm when JFK wOn an electiOn with hiS father'S help.
自从约翰・肯尼迪靠着父亲帮忙在选举中舞弊以后 情况都大同小异
- YOu're uncOmfOrtable I mentiOn JFK? - NO, I dOn't like making twO tripS.
- 听这话你心里不舒服 - 不是，我只是不想跑两趟
YOu AmericanS, yOu IOve yOur herOeS. A hOliday fOr Columbus?
你们这些美国佬 你们爱你们的英雄 美国有个哥伦布节吧？
He makeS the wrOng turn and wipeS Out an indigenOuS peOple.
他只是走错了路 然后把原住民都给消灭了
- KnOw what he waS IOOking fOr? - Tell me.
- 你知道哥伦布想找什么吗？ - 你肯定会告诉我的
GOld, SuppOSedly fOr Queen ISabella.
金子  就像在伊莎贝拉女王时代
DOn't think the MediciS didn't want SOme. What did Italy need gOld fOr?
如果梅第奇重返意大利 他也会参加这行动的 意大利要黄金来干什么呢
The IOng-diStance Slave trade, baSed in Venice.
为了在威尼斯作长期的奴隶贸易
Venice. That'S where theSe brickS...
威尼斯 就在那里
- YOu were Saying SOmething? - NO.
- 你刚才说什么？ - 什么也没说
DOn't StOp. I'm intereSted.
别停下 我很有兴趣
PleaSe, I'm cOnfuSed. My EngliSh...
对不起 我有点昏了头 我的英语
What dO yOu knOw abOut my gOld?
关于我的金子你都知道些什么？
- I dOn't...  - DOn't even think abOut lying tO me.
- 我不知道 - 别想着能骗我
OK. I heard a rumOur abOut a heiSt in Venice.
好, 好, 我听到谣言 发生在威尼斯的一起劫案
35 milliOn, in brickS, with a BalineSe dancer imprint.
价值3千5百万美金的金砖上面刻着巴厘舞娘
- WhO have yOu tOld?  - NO One, I Swear tO GOd!
- 你还告诉过谁？ - 谁也没告诉 我对天发誓
- YOu Swear tO GOd? - YOu're crazy. I Swear tO GOd, I didn't.
- 对天发誓？ - 你疯了？我对天发誓  我没有
Well, then, I gueSS I believe yOu.
我应该相信你
Let'S putt it. Putt, nOt drive.
推杆 不要打
Very gOOd. YOu can get it. I knOw yOu can dO it.
很好  如果你去做的话 我就知道你行的
- Here tO See Skinny Pete. - He'S Over there.
- 我要见Skinny Pete - 他在那边
ThankS, man.
谢谢 伙计
DOn't Stare. He dOeSn't like peOple Staring.
不要盯着眼看 他不喜欢别人盯着他看
Stare at what?
盯着什么？
That waS gOOd. Try that One.I knOw yOu'll get that One.
做得好 再来一次 我知道你很快会成功的
- That waS great. - Skinny Pete.
- 很好  - Skinny Pete
- YO, Charlie.  - What'S up, man?
- Charlie  - 最近怎样？
WaS I right abOut the gOld?
关于那些黄金 我猜对了？
I'm nOt here fOr that. We need SOme SupplieS.
我不是来说这的 我们需要一些补给品
Baby, gO relax. GO relax!
宝贝 先去休息一下
- SupplieS.  - What'S wrOng?
- 补给 - 有问题吗？
SOme nitrOmOn...
一些尼特罗明
- SOme nitrOmOn primer.  - What'S wrOng?
- 一些尼特罗明 雷管  - 你怎么了？
NOthing, I'm cOOI. I'm great. I juSt need a big can Of...
没什么 我很好 我需要一些 呃 大罐的
...nitrOmOn primer, detOnating cOrd,
罗明 雷管 导爆索
twO triple-charger chemical grenadeS and a launcher.
两个三线化学榴弹和一个引爆器
- Right, like I had tOld yOu earlier. - All right.
- 对 就像 呃 像我之前跟你说的一样 - 好的
- COSt yOu abOut five GS. - DOne. ThankS. SOrry abOut that.
- 那大概要五千  - 成交 谢谢 兄弟 不好意思
- All right, man. Peace. - COme On.
- 好的 兄弟 别生气   - 走吧
Get Out.
出来
There.
那里
Vance haS SOmething tO tell yOu.
Vance 有话对你说
GO On.
说话
A cOuple Of weekS back...
几星期以前
...I waS wOrking in yOur cOuSin'S ShOp.
我在你表兄开的店工作
A guy cOme in aSking abOut gOld brickS with BalineSe dancer On.
一个人进来询问那批舞娘金砖的事
- What did yOu tell him? - That I'd Seen the brickS.
- 你跟他说什么了 - 我说我见过这些金砖
- I'm SOrry. - What did thiS man IOOk like?
- 对不起  - 那人长什么样
He had IOng black hair with tattOO On hiS neck.
他有又长又黑的头发 脖子上有一大片纹身
He muSt have weighed  at leaSt 400 pOundS.
他肯定有400磅重
I knOw that guy.
我知道是谁
Baby, gO relax.
宝贝 自己去玩
- DO yOu knOw whO I am? - YOu're Mashkov.
- 你知道我是谁吗 - 你是Mashkov
Right. YOu were aSking abOut the gOld brickS with the BalineSe dancer On.
没错 你去查问过那些 舞娘金砖的事
Why?
告诉我原因
Steve juSt cOnfirmed  hiS eight O'clOck dinner reServatiOn.
Steve打电话来 他在餐厅预订了8点的位子
- Let'S gO Over it.  - GaS the guardS. DOOrS Open, 8.15.
-  我们再复习一次行动计划 - 迷倒守卫 8点15打开门
- Safe pOpped by 8.25.  - LOaded, 8.35. Out, 8.45.
- 保险箱8点25打开 - 8点35装车完毕  8点45离开
Straight tO UniOn StatiOn.
直奔联合车站
Only green lightS, reSt Of city'S red. COpS Stuck in traffic.
一路绿灯 其他地方都是红灯 警察也像其他人一样在塞车
Train leaveS at 10. CarS muSt be abOard by 9.30. Timing muSt be exact.
火车10点离站9点30分保证车子全部进入货柜  时间完全正确
- Let'S get ready. - Let'S get it.
- 去准备一下  - 行动吧
WOw, that iS a nice car. SOrry, ROb. COaSt iS clear, guyS.
哇  好漂亮的车 对不起 ROb 他走了 伙计们
ThiS iS it. MOment Of truth.
是时候了   成败就在此举
What the hell iS thiS? Shit!
这是怎么回事？  该死！
Steve's neighbour's throwing a party.
Steve的邻居在开派对
- Are yOu here fOr the Baker party, Sir?  - NO.
- 先生 你是来参加贝克的派对的吗 - 不是
We're nOt blOwing any gateS tOnight, guyS. TOO many witneSSeS.
伙计们 今晚我们没法炸门了 太多目击者了
- Stella. - I knOw...
- Stella. - 我知道
I'm late fOr my date.
我的约会要迟到了
YOu've gOt tO be charming. We need him tO aSk yOu Out again. SOrry.
对 展现你的魅力 你要让他再约你出来 对不起
Let'S get Out Of the Street.
请不要站在马路上
- I can't imagine yOu dOing that. - What'S that mean?
- 真不可想象你竟然这样做了 - 什么意
Well, yOu dOn't really Seem the adventurOuS type, yOu knOw.
你看起来 不像那种喜欢冒险的女孩
DOn't let the cable unifOrm thrOw yOu.
别被我的工作服给迷惑了
I waSn't making aSSumptiOnS.
我从来不想当然
- I've made SOme abOut yOu. - Oh, really? And?
- 我倒是知道 你有些想  - 真的吗？ 然后？
YOu're juSt gOing tO have tO wait and See.
还是等着瞧吧
Why wait? Let'S gO back tO my place. NO aSSumptiOnS.
为什么要等？  不如我们马上验证一下  到我家去吧 不用推断了…
NOt tOnight. It'S late. I ShOuld gO hOme.
今晚不行 太晚了 我得回家
- YOu have a cable cOmpany curfew?  - NO.
- 公司有作息规定吗  - 没有
I've made SOme bad callS in the paSt. We ShOuld take thiS SIOwer.
但我有些不好的回忆  我们得慢慢来
LOvely dinner, Sparkling cOnverSatiOn.Still dOn't truSt me?
这里饭菜可口 我们言谈甚欢 你难道还不信任我吗？
I truSt everyOne. It'S the devil inSide them I dOn't truSt.
我什么人都相信  只是不相信人们心中的邪恶
That'S an intereSting Saying. Where'd yOu pick that up?
这话有意思 你哪里听回来的？
- Can't remember. - I knew a guy whO Said it juSt like that.
- 忘了 - 有个人也说过 一模一样的话
- Really? - Yeah.
- 真的？ - 对
He'S the Only perSOn I've ever heard Say that. HiS name waS JOhn Bridger.
只听他说过 他的名字叫John Bridger
- YOu're hurting me.  - He had a daughter abOut yOur age.
- 你抓疼我了  - 他有个女儿和你差不多年纪
Let gO.
放开我的手
I knew there waS SOmething familiar abOut yOu.
我就觉得你们俩有点像
YOu're exactly like yOur Old man. I liked him, tOO.
知道吗？你跟你老爸一样 我也很喜欢他
I liked him right up until the minute I ShOt him.
直到杀了他那一刻 我都挺喜欢他
WhO are yOu wOrking with?
你到底为谁工作？
She'S with uS.
她是我们的人
- The gang'S all here.  - The Only thing wOrSe than a thief...
- 齐聚一堂  -  比作贼还差的是
...iS a cOward.
懦夫
Then yOu ShOuld've Seen the way yOur daddy begged fOr hiS life.
你真该见见令尊 向我求饶的样子
- He'S nOt wOrth it.  - Put a leaSh On yOur cat.
- 不值得  - 把你的猫栓好了
NOt bad, Charlie.
不错 Charlie
YOu have nO idea hOw hard it iS fOr me nOt tO kill yOu nOw.
你可知道我全力控制自己 没扑过去宰了你
YOu knOw better than that. YOu can't let emOtiOn intO theSe thingS.
有多么困难吗？ 你应该知道不能感情用事
It waSn't emOtiOn when yOu ShOt John and left uS?
你杀了John并置我们于死地 算不算感情用事？
That waSn't abOut emOtiOn. It waS abOut a IOt Of gOld.
这和感情无关 和一大堆我想要的金子有关
Anything yOu think yOu deServed, yOu didn't.
你老认为自己理所应得 不是这样的
DOn't talk abOut right and wrOng with me. I dOn't give a Shit. OK?
别跟我谈论是非对错  我根本不屑一顾 好吗？
YOu gOt yOur cardS, I gOt mine. We made Our play, I came Out On tOp.
你有你的牌  我有我的招 我们公平竞争  最后我获胜了
If yOu want tO Start the game up again, that'S fine with me.
如果你还想再较量一把 我随时奉陪
What iS yOur play here, really?
你们到底想玩什么招？
COme On, what dO yOu think?
你们是怎么计划的？
YOu'll try tO take Out my guardS? I have five that yOu dOn't knOw abOut.
首先要拿掉我的警卫，对吧？ 你们不知道我有5名警卫
YOu'll have Lyle hack the SyStem? I'll change it tOmOrrOw mOrning.
你们想让 Lyle 破解系统 但明天早上 我就会把整个系统换掉
What waS yOur final mOve? Have Bridger'S daughter try tO crack my Safe?
最后一步是什么？ 让Bridger的女儿打开保险箱？
That'S very pOetic, but I juSt dOn't think She'll get anywhere near it.
真是非常浪漫写意 可惜我见不到 她根本没机会靠近保险箱
Same Old Steve. AlwayS thinking defenSively.
你一点没变 Steve 总是想着防守
That'S why yOu're alwayS number twO.
所以你永远成不了老大
- HOw'S that? - YOu've gOt nO imaginatiOn.
- 你怎么会这么想？ - 你缺乏想像力
COuldn't even decide what tO buy. BOught what everyOne elSe wanted.
拿着这么多钱 也不知道怎么花 只会买点俗气之极的东西
- Try thiS. That gOld iS already gOne. - BullShit.
- 那你就继续想象吧 好吗  - 金子全没了
It'S Over, Charlie. I'm trying tO mOve the laSt twO brickS.
金子全没了 Charlie 我正在处理最后两块金砖
YOu want tO cOme after me Over a cOuple Of IOuSy brickS? Be my gueSt.
想不想跟我去看看 那两块烂金砖？ 真的，我请你作客
But yOu're Off tO a bad Start becauSe yOu juSt blew the element Of SurpriSe.
真的，你的行动 有个糟糕的开场 因为你已经无法再攻我不备
SurpriSed?
攻你不备吧？
Lt'S Over when I Say it'S Over.
我说什么时候结束 才算结束
Are yOu all right, Sir?
你没事吧？先生
HOw yOu dOing?
你怎么了？
GOOd.
挺好
COnSidering the fact I'm dOing all Of thiS fOr a man I barely knew.
我在想 我的所作的为都是 为了一个很不了解的人
YOu knOw what bOthered me all thOSe yearS?
知道那些年我的烦恼是什么吗？
It waS that whenever he'd call me tO tell me he waS On SOme jOb,
就是他给我电话说他又重操旧业
I knew yOu were right there with him.
我就知道你正在他身边
YOu gOt tO knOw him a IOt better than I did.
你一定比我更了解他
DOeSn't mean he waSn't thinking abOut yOu.
并不代表他心里没你
- WOuld be nice if it waS true. - It iS.
- 如果是真的就太好了 - 是真的
He alwayS regretted nOt having been a gOOd enOugh father tO yOu.
他总是悔恨自己不是个好父亲
- HOw dO yOu knOw? - BecauSe he tOld me.
- 你怎么知道？ - 你怎么知道？
What did yOu dO tO yOur hand?
你的手怎么了？
- I punched Steve.  - Why dO yOu get tO punch him?
- 我教训了Steve - 为什么你能动手我却不可以？
'CauSe thOSe handS are way tOO valuable.
因为你那双手太值钱了
YOu OK?
你还好吗？
There'll be nOthing left Of that if yOu keep rubbing it.
再擦下去什么都被你擦没了
Tell Mr Frizelli we'll see him at eight.
告诉Frizelli先生 我们8点去见他
- He'S flying the cOOp. - When?
- 他正准备逃之夭夭 - 什么时候？
HiS Security guardcalled fOr a helicOpter at 4 p.m.
他的警卫下午4点叫了直升飞机
And an armOured car at five.
5点有部装甲汽车开到他家
There'S a cargO plane, departing LAX at 8 p.m. TO MexicO City.
有一架货机8点由洛杉矶国际机场起飞 飞往墨西哥
What if he'S mOving the Safe aS a diverSiOn?
可能他搬动保险箱只是个障眼法
- We crack it, the gOld'S SOmewhere elSe. - Steve wOn't let it Out Of hiS Sight.
- 我们打开之后却是空的 金子在其他地方 - Steve不可能让金子离开他的眼皮
It'll be in that truck and he'll watch it frOm the helicOpter.
金子就在那辆卡车上 他会从直升机上 寸步不离地监控着
- The gOld'S headed tO MexicO? - WhO knOwS?
- 他会从直升机上 寸步不离地监控着  - 谁知道是哪？
- SIOw dOwn. ThiS iS gOOd newS fOr uS. - What dO yOu mean?
- 慢来  其实对我们来说是件好事 - 你什么意思？
NOw the Safe haS cOme tO uS. We're gOing tO bOOSt it in tranSit.
现在保险箱就要出现在我们面前 我们要在运输途中动手
He cOuld take a dOzen rOuteS.
到机场有很多条路线
We dOn't knOw which. We can't take Out an armOured truck at ruSh hOur.
我们不知道是哪一条 交通高峰期间我们对付不了装甲卡车
We're already Set up tO dO it. GridlOck every rOute except the One we chOOSe.
我们已经安排好了 封锁其他行车路线 除了我们指定的那条
FOrce that truck tO gO where we want.
强迫卡车行进到我们安排好的位置上
Where dO we want it tO gO? We'd IOSe a ShOOt up.
我们要让卡车开到哪里去  我们会失手的
We dO it like The Italian Job.
我们可以象在T意大利那样干
- Why'd yOu dO it?  - DO what?
- 你为什么要这么干？- 干什么？
- Yevhen. YOu didn't have tO clip him. - We didn't clip anybOdy.
- Yevhen 你没必要废了他 - 我们什么人也没废过
Yevhen'S cOuSin iS under the impreSSiOn yOu did.
Yevhen的表弟对此可是深信不疑
Why?
他为什么这么想？
BecauSe yOu wanted tO knOw abOut the gOld.
因为你对那批刻着舞娘的金块很有兴趣
YOu tOld him that?
你告诉他了？
One thing I knOw, never meSS with MOther Nature,
我给你个忠告永远别去招惹
mOther-in-lawS, Or mOther-freaking UkrainianS.
反复无常的乌克兰人
LOOk, I need a favOur.
听着 你要帮我一个忙
Had a hiccup laSt night. Need SOme help. MOre handS-On. IntereSted?
昨晚出了点问题 需要找你作个帮手 有没有兴趣？
COuld be, but I dOn't like tO be kept in the dark. If I'm in, I'm in.
可我不希望暗地里加入 我加入就要成为正式的一份子
- OK, you're in. - All right.
- 好的 算你一份  - 好的
- What dO yOu think? - ThiS'll wOrk. Let'S gO.
- 怎么样？- 没问题，走吧
YOu're amazing. It'S a wOrk Of geniuS.
你真了不起 天才的杰作
- YOu OK? - JuSt give me a mOment.
- 你没事吧？ - 让我休息一会
- NOw?  - I'm inSerting thiS pin intO the detOnatOr.
- 现在？ - 我要把这东西插入雷管里
If the braSS tOucheS the SideS, we'll bOth be the laSt peOple we ever See.
如果上面的铜皮碰到雷管 我们就会玩完的
Take all the time yOu need.
那你愿意休息多久 就休多久吧
- Hey, Charlie. - What?
- 嘿，Charlie？ - 怎么了？
I IOve yOu, man.
我爱你 伙计
I IOve yOu, tOO.
我也爱你
He'S gOing tO be On train 59 fOr New OrleanS.
他会出现在开往新奥尔良的59次车上
YOu Sure the SOurce iS gOOd?
消息来源可靠吗？
I'm Sure.
绝对可靠
Check pOSitiOnS. Napster?
Napster 报告各自位置
I'm in pOSitiOn.
我已经就位
- HandSOme ROb? - In pOSitiOn. Everything'S quiet, Charlie.
- 帅哥ROb？ - 我们已经就位 周围很安静 Charlie
Wrench?
扳手？
Set.
布置妥当
We've gOt an uninvited viSitOr. There'S a mOtOrcycle guard fOllOwing the truck.
有不速之客 卡车后有摩托手押车
We'll deal with it.
我们会处理的
- WhO are they? - What's wrong?
- 这些车是什么？ - 怎么了？
YOu wOn't believe thiS. He'S brOught in three armOured truckS.
真不敢相信 他叫了三部装甲卡车来
It'S a Shell game nOw.
真真假假的障眼法
I can't re-rOute if I dOn't knOw which tO re-rOute.
老大，我不知道是哪部车 可没法控制车的行进路线
Follow the one Steve follows by helicopter.
就是直升机 跟着的那辆车
He'll never let that gOld Out Of hiS Sight.
他说过永远不会让金子离开他的视线
UnleSS he'S playing uS. And he iS.
除非他耍我们 要不就是那部车
OK, let'S gO! MOve it Out!
好的 出发  动身
Here we gO. They're pulling Out.
来了 他们动身了
NapSter, pull up the traffic cameraS yOu're watching.
NapSter 移动监控摄像机
Where's the first camera they go past?
卡车通过的第一个路口是哪里？
- Vine and Yucca. - See which One'S riding IOw.
- 维恩和加科路口 - 看一下哪部车车身较低
FirSt in line... FirSt twO are the Same, SO...
第一部是… 第二部也一样，所以…
HOuStOn, we have Our truck. Number 128.
休斯敦，目标找到，车号128
We're mOving Out.
我们跟在后面
Three Kilo Bob to Two Fox Mike, we're heading to the airport.
三千 呼叫 双狐 我们正前往机场
OK, guys, truck 128 has turned right heading west.
好了伙计们 128号车转右向西去了
GridlOck time.
堵塞交通
We've craShed.
系统崩溃了
It'S nOt a craSh.
不是崩溃
- We've gOt pOwer. - I can't IOg in.
- 也没有停电 - 也没有停电
They're abOut tO hit a detOur and be Sent yOur way.
准备让他们兜个大圈 然后送到门口上来
YOu'll never Shut dOwn the real NapSter.
你们永远无法关闭真正的Napster
What'S yOur prOblem?
你有问题吗？
- Truck 128, what is your progress? - Traffic's out of control.
- 128号车 你们进展如何？  - 这里交通失控
We've got to look for another route.
我们得走另一条路
Check the pOlice band.
监听警察的通讯
OK, I'm Opening up a Space On Highland.
好的，我给你们开出一条通道
- Get uS Out Of here. - I'm trying.
- 快离开这里 - 我正在想办法
And he'S taking it.
中招了
POlice are Saying cOmputerS are dOwn at traffic cOntrOI.
警察说交通管制中心的电脑崩溃了
Nice, Charlie. What are yOu up tO?
干得好 Charlie 你到底想干什么？
GO back.
回头
I nOw cOmmand yOu tO turn left.
我现在命令你左转
COme On, take the left.
快点，往左转
Yeah, yOu did. YOu did.
听话 真听话
Give uS the flag.
给我们指示
MetrO juSt paSSed thrOugh the StatiOn. YOu are clear fOr 90 SecOndS. GO.
地铁刚刚离站 你们有90秒的时间 走
COme On, Steve.
来了
Steve
30 SecOndS and cOunting.
还剩30秒
15 SecOndS, yOu're blOcked in Or yOu're paint On the train.
还有15秒 不成功便成仁
COme On, cOme On!
快 快
Stay On me. ThiS'll be tight!
跟紧我 这就对了
- GO, gO, gO. - YOu're gOing tO StOp there.
- 快 快 快 - 乘客们到站了
- OK, guyS, cOming intO pOSitiOn. - Stay cOOI.
- 好了伙计们 他就来了  - 冷静
Ten, nine...
10  9...
... eight, seven...
... 8... 7...
... six, five...
... 6... 5...
...fOur...
...4...
- DOn't IOSe him. - ... three...
- 别跟丢 - ...3...
... two, one...
... 2...1...
What?!
怎么了
Damn.
该死
What the fuck happened tO my truck?!
我的车去哪了？
- It blew thrOugh the Street. - Get under there.
- 街上发生爆炸 - 到那里
- We have anOther prOblem. - What?
- 我们还有一个问题 - 怎么了？
- ThiS iSn't the WOrthingtOn 1000. - What?
- 这不是渥新顿1000 - 什么？
He Switched SafeS On uS.
他换了个保险箱
- Can yOu dO it? - It'S ISraeli made.
- 你能搞定吗？ - 以色列出产的
It'S gOt a glaSS relOck SyStem. There'S a pane Of glaSS here.
带有玻璃防盗系统  门后面是一大块玻璃
If I dOn't drill perfectly, Steel rOdS Snap intO place and we can't Open it.
如果钻孔的位置稍有偏差 内部的钢条把门锁死之后
Then we're up Shit creek.
就无法打开保险箱 我们的麻烦可就大了
I think I juSt cracked the glaSS. I dOn't think it brOke, thOugh.
我刚才碰到玻璃了 应该还没碎
I can't drill it again. I have tO dO it by tOuch.
我不能再钻了 现在只能凭触觉了
I can't get thrOugh. The train'S blOcking the tunnel.
我过不去 地铁把通道堵住了
- Where dOeS the MetrO Rail emerge? - Eleventh and Fig.
- 地铁从哪里上到地面？ - 11大街和菲格大街交叉处
Meet at Eleventh and FigarO and dOuble back tO HOllywOOd and Highland. Hurry.
在11大街与菲格大街交叉处碰头 然后再兜回到出事地点 快点
Baggage for train 22 now available at carousel 4.
22次车行李已在4号传送带
I can't dO thiS. I need a drill Or a bOreScOpe tO get in there.
我不行了 我得用钻头管道镜之类的东西
- COme On, Charlie. - YOu can dO thiS.
- 快点 Charlie - 你能行的
Slide.
快点
- DOn't yOu want tO See inSide? - AbSOlutely.
- 不想看看里面吗？ - 当然想
NapSter, 13 acrOSS, 4 high, 4 deep.
NapSter 每排13个 高度4 深度4
- That'S 208 brickS. - HOw much?
- 总共208块金砖 - 价值多少？
- 2.7 milliOn. - What?!
- 270万 - 什么？
NO, it'S 27. That'S 27 milliOn.
不, 是2千7百万
That'S 27 milliOn dOllarS wOrth Of gOld.
价值2千7百万
GOt the HOly Spirit. YOu ShOuld get On it, it'S a gOOd train.
老天保佑 你们继续吧 这趟车真不错
What dO yOu think, JOhn?
有什么感想 JOhn?
- 27 milliOn. - Say it again.
- 2千7百万 - 再说一次
We've gOt twO mOtOrcycleS On uS, Charlie.
有两部摩托跟着我们
Three MiniS heading eaSt tOwardS the LA river.
三部小车通过下水道 向东前往洛杉矶河
StOp them befOre they get tO the Street.
别让他们到达地面
Shit!
该死
Here we gO.
到了
Open yOur dOOr.
开门
COme On, guyS. We're mOving.
跟上，伙计们
There!
那里
Hey, cOme On. Get dOwn!
嘿 快 快
COme On!
快
Where are yOu gOing?
你要去哪？
I'll take Steve. GO tO UniOn StatiOn. I'll meet yOu there.
我要去对付Steve 你们直接去联合车站
Stay On him.
跟住他
I'm Opening up a SpOt On LOwer Grand.
我给你开一条通道
I knOw it'S yOu, Charlie.
我就知道是你 Charlie
Take yOur next left.
下一个路口左转
Nice mOve, Steve.
跟的够紧  Steve
Get Out! Get Out!
出去 出去
I Said get Out!
你给我出去
YOu gOt Mini COOperS in there, right?
你有9辆迷你库柏斯？
DOn't wOrry abOut them. I'll give yOu five grand tO put me inSide.
你别担心 如果你让我进去 我付你5千美元
Buy yOur girlfriend SOmething nice.
给你的女朋友买点好东西
Half nOw, half when yOu help me unlOad.
先付一半 等我下车再付另一半
I've gOt tO hand it tO yOu. YOu played thiS One pretty Smart.
我对你深表敬佩 你可真是机关算尽
DecOy truckS, yOu Switched SafeS, the helicOpter rOutine. Pretty gOOd.
真真假假的卡车 换了型号的保险箱 直升飞机押运 这几手真是漂亮无比
NOw I've gOt the gOld, yOu've gOt nOthing.
只可惜金子已经归我 而你已一无所有
I've gOt thiS, SO cut the crap and give me my gOddamn gOld!
我有这个 少跟我废话 把金子还给我
- WhO are yOu? - I am Mashkov.
- 你是什么人？ - 我叫Mashkov
- YOu killed my cOuSin Yevhen. - YOu've gOt tO have SOme inSurance.
- 你杀了我的表兄Yevhen - 你应该买份保险
He waS already dead when I arrived. He dealt with unSavOury peOple.
我到那里他已经死了 他常和很多难缠的家伙打交道
- ThiS guy'S trying tO play yOu. - YOu were right. NO imaginatiOn.
- 这个家伙在玩弄你们 - 你真的 缺乏想像力
There'S a IOt Of gOld in there. Only we've gOt gunS. I'll make yOu a gOOd deal.
那边有很多金子 这里只有我们有枪 我们作笔好买卖
I've already made my deal.
我已经作完买卖了
- What dO yOu want? - YOu knOw thiS waS never abOut gOld.
- 你想干什么？ - 你知道这和金子没有关系
Whatever helpS yOu Sleep at night, Sweetheart.
希望你晚上能睡得好 宝贝
Bitch. Charlie, cOme On, Charlie!
婊子 Charlie 别这样 Charlie
That I IOved.
我喜欢
I'll dOuble whatever he'S given yOu, juSt dOn't ShOOt me.
我付你们双倍的价 别枪杀我
DOn't wOrry, I'm nOt gOing tO ShOOt yOu. I'm gOing tO take yOu tO my wOrkplace.
别担心 我不会枪杀你的 我会带你到我的工场去
I think yOu'll be intereSted in my machinery.
我的某些机器 你会很有兴趣的
Oh, cOme On.
别这样
GuyS, I want tO make a tOaSt.
伙计们 我们碰一杯
TO JOhn Bridger. The mOSt brilliant maSter planner Of all. Father and friend.
为了JOhn Bridger 最睿智的策划者 父亲和朋友
Stella was right.It wasn't about the money.
斯特拉说得对 这不是钱的问题
Of course, that didn't stop the guys from having some fun.
当然 无法阻止这帮家伙去找乐子
Handsome Rob got his Aston Martin.
帅哥 Ro买了Aston Martin
Took it for a ride to break it in.
用它兜风破纪录
He got off with a warning.
他只受到警告
Left Ear got his dream house in Spain
左耳在西班牙北部买下了梦寐以求的豪宅
with a room just for his shoes.
有一间房专门放他的鞋
Lyle finally made the cover of Wired magazine.
莱尔最终登上杂志的封面
- Are yOu really the NapSter? - YeS, I am.
- 你真的是Napster？ - 是的 我就是
And he got that kick-ass stereo he wanted.
一直渴望的音响也买回来了
WOuld yOu liSten tO SOmething?
你帮我听点东西 行吗？
With speakers so loud they could blow a woman's clothes off.
音响带着巨大的喇叭 真能帮女人宽衣解带
If yOu wOuld.
你能不能
And me? I took John Bridger's advice.
至于我 我采纳了John Bridger的建议
I found somebody I want to spend the rest of my life with,
找到了与我共渡余生的人
and I'm goingto hold on to her forever.
我要和她永远相偎相依